# BRYANT VAN ORDEN

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

I am an Eagle Scout, returned missionary, and a 2 year in a row multi-University Hackathon winner with a 4.0 in college. I am highly motivated and dedicated to delivering exceptional customer service. I am a highly intelligent individual with an IQ range of 133-149. I can speak, read, and write Spanish and have acquired many skills while serving in 3 different countries. I also Created the Machine Learning Companion App on the play store.

#### **HOBBIES:**

Coding, Reading, Board Games, Hiking, Swimming, Time with family and friends, Fishing, and Podcasts

#### Contact:

PHONE: (480) - 353 - 9004

LINKEDIN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/bryant

van-orden-722818252

EMAIL: <u>SUPERMANISMEBVO123@GMAIL.COM</u>

### **EDUCATION**

#### **BRIGHAM YOUNG UNIVERSITY:**

2022 - NOW

I am a sophomore with a bachelor's degree in software engineering. I have a 4.0 in all my classes. I was always top of the class. I excelled in every aspect of coding.

#### **CERTIFICATES**

- Advanced SQL for data Scientists
- SQL: Data Reporting and Analysis
- First place award of the BYUI fall Hackathon 20222
- First place BYUI multi university Hackathon fall 2023
- Best use of Google Cloud Hackathon fall 2023
- BYUI Coding Certificate (job ready)

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

CHURCH OF JESUS CHRIST OF LATTER DAY SAINTS Database Engineering Intern

Jan 2023-Now

I worked on hundreds of bugs and added many new features to over 130 different worldwide education system reports written in SQL. These reports were primarily in SSRS and Power BI. I worked on moving these reports to Power BI and keeping them updated.

#### **NEIGHBORHOOD NEXUS**

Primary Engineer

October 2023

I created a multiplatform app using dart and flutter for the BYUI Multi University Hackathon winning First place in our competitive category and Overall winner of the Best use of Google Cloud.

#### HOME CARE PULSE

Software Engineering Student Contractor 2022 Fall–2022 Fall

I and a team of 3 other students worked with Home Care pulse to make a Machine Learning application that could predict their data in a CSV file into the future and output it in interactive charts. I coded the entire back end of our app in python.

SERVICE [unpaid] Missionary July 2020–July 2022

## SKILLS

